Jevan Bisla



UX/UI Designer.

Profile

An accomplished and confident designer with initiative and a can-do work ethic, with a broad range of design skills. I'm currently expanding my knowledge learning UX/UI design in an intensive training program for UX Designers, specialising in UX process and methodology that includes the whole design process, research, development, visual design, and prototyping at Career Foundry.

Focused on learning & creating engaging, thoughtful user experiences from inception to development. Driven with a passion for design, solving problems, wanting to push for design that puts the user first. Empathising with people to create unique engaging experiences.

Experience

Freelance Design & Illustration

(2014 - Current)

Whilst studying and working I have worked independently for a number of clients on a variety of projects spanning print & digital, prioritising a number of projects managing my workload.

Salamandra Uk

Graphic Designer

(Feb 2018 - Feb 2019)

At Salamandra I became an efficient Junior Designer with a keen eye of detail and have a growing conviction in my design decisions. I gained experience working in a fast-paced environment with tight deadlines, creating high-quality print & digital work. Hit the ground running, attending client meetings, working both independently & collaboratively contributing creative across projects. Communicating ideas with animators, marketing departments, printers, and developers.

Skills

Adobe Creative Suite Sketch

UI Design Branding Flinto

Illustration UX Design Webflow

Prototyping Invision Figma

Education

Career Foundry

(Oct 2019 - Current)
Certified UX Design. Intensive course specializing in user-centered design and research-driven approaches to design.

University of Westminster

(Sept 2015 - May 2017)
Ba Hons in Visual Communication - 2.1

Contact

jevanbisla@gmail.com

07917017987

<u>LinkedIn</u>

and methodology that includes the whole design process, research, development, visual design, and prototyping at Career Foundry.

Focused on learning & creating engaging, thoughtful user experiences from inception to development. Driven with a passion for design, solving problems, wanting to push for design that puts the user first. Empathising with people to create unique engaging experiences.

Experience

Freelance Design & Illustration

(2014 - Current)

Whilst studying and working I have worked independently for a number of clients on a variety of projects spanning print & digital, prioritising a number of projects managing my workload.

Salamandra Uk

Graphic Designer

(Feb 2018 - Feb 2019)

At Salamandra I became an efficient Junior Designer with a keen eye of detail and have a growing conviction in my design decisions. I gained experience working in a fast-paced environment with tight deadlines, creating high-quality print & digital work. Hit the ground running, attending client meetings, working both independently & collaboratively contributing creative across projects. Communicating ideas with animators, marketing departments, printers, and developers.

Illustration UX Design Webflow

Prototyping Invision Figma

Education

Career Foundry

(Oct 2019 - Current)

Certified UX Design. Intensive course specializing in user-centered design and research-driven approaches to design.

University of Westminster

(Sept 2015 - May 2017)

Ba Hons in Visual Communication - 2.1

Contact

- jevanbisla@gmail.com
- 07917017987
- <u>LinkedIn</u>